hi this is Mark this is English
conversation practice conversations at
an airport let's preview where are you
going what takes you there I'm going for
business I'm going for pleasure
how long will you stay I'm not going I'm
arriving where are you arriving from I
want to go
I plan to travel around for about a
month I hope you have a safe and fun
trip okay let's practice the
conversations two people are talking
while waiting for their flights
where are you going I'm off to the
States
what takes you there I'm going for
business and Gia I'm going to Thailand
are you also going for business
No I'm going for pleasure how long will
you stay
I'm planning to stay for about ten days
have a safe trip thanks you too
two people meet at an airport lunch
counter one person is departing and the
other person is just arriving
where are you going I'm not going I'm
arriving
where are you arriving from I'm
returning from Australia
Wow that sounds great how long were you
there I was there just over a year did
you like it there yes I loved it
what did you like most
the people were so nice and of course
the food was delicious how was the
weather
the weather was great in Australia not
too hot and not too cold
oh I want to go you should go
well how about cheetah where are you
going I'm going to India
how long will you stay in India I plan
to travel around for about a month
I hope you have a safe and fun trip
thanks so much
okay great
let's review where are you going what
takes you there I am going for business
I'm going for a pleasure how long will
you stay I'm not going I'm arriving
where are you arriving from I want to go
I plan to travel around for about a
month I hope you have a safe and fun
trip
okay great job we'll see you next time
take it easy bye